export const QuizDataJava = [
    {
        question: 'What is a class in java?',
        options: ["class is a blue print from which individual objects are created. A class can contain fields and methods to describe the behavior of an object.",
            "class is a special data type.",
            "class is used to allocate memory to a data type.",
            "none of the above."],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the size of int variable?",
        options: ["8 bit", "16 bit", "32 bit", "64 bit"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default value of byte variable?",
        options: ["0", "0.0", "null", "Hundefined"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is an applet?",
        options: ["An applet is a Java program that runs in a Web browser.", "Applet is a standalone java program.",
            "Applet is a tool.", "Applet is a run time environment."],
        answer: 1
    },
];
export const QuizDataJavaScript = [
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
        options: ["Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
        options: ["var", "let", "Both", "None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
        options: ["const", "let", "var", "constant"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What year was JavaScript launched?",
        options: ["1996", "1995", "1994", "none of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
];
export const QuizDataReact = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
        options: ["npx create-react-app appname", "	npm install create-react-app", "npx install create-react-app -g", "install â€“ l create-react-app"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        options: ["	Create", "Extends",
            "Inherits",
            "Delete"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        options: ["3000", "4000", "4500", "5000"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following valid component return type of React ?",
        options: ["1", "2", "5", "3"],
        answer: 1
    },
];